



#### **PERSONAL**

- Name
  Yi Ting Lan
- **Mobile** 0921763276
- Portfolio

  www.delphinelan.com

#### LANGUAGES

English Intermediate

Japanese Beginner

Mandrain Native

Taiwanese Advanced

### INTERESTS

- Painting
- Reading

# YI TING LAN

Yi Ting Lan is a Taiwan designer specialising in UI Design, Graphic Design, and Digital Design. I am a dependable team worker in the company. Even if I have never been exposed to work or software I never stop learned and get myself into the situation quickly. I continue to improve the necessary skills in the workplace, and also like to collect relevant information. I also hope that will be more development in the future. I have a very positive attitude and full of ideals and ambitions for my work.

### WORK EXPERIENCE

Aug 2019 - Present Senior Visual Designer

Anue 鉅亨金融科技股份有限公司(鉅亨網), Taipei

Internal Website and APP UI Design by sketch.

Some Advertising Banner and Campaingn page production .

Jun 2015 - Jul 2019 Web Designer

AMC 空中美語, Taipei

Internal and External Website Design based on the ability of html and css.

Responsive website design based on bootstrap.

DM > POSTER Design based on the ability of photoshop and

illustrator.

Apr 2012 - May 2015 Graphic Designer

FASHION ADVERTISING CREATIONS INC., Taipei

Internal and External Website Design based on the ability of html and css.

DM > POSTER Design based on the ability of photoshop and illustrator.

Film Editing Producing vedio by After effects and premiere

Oct 2010 - Aug 2011 Graphic Designer

偉氏國際有限公司, Taipei

DM > POSTER Design based on the ability of photoshop and illustrator.

## EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

Sep 2006 - Jul 2010 Bachelor degree of Digital Multimedia Arts

Shih Hsin University, SHU, Taipei

3D Building and animation design skills

- Creative strategy animation planning.
- Producing visual effects Video.



Experienced	*	*	*	*	*	
Experienced	*	*	*	*	*	
Experienced	*	*	*	*	*	
Experienced	*	*	*	*	*	
Skillful	*	*	*	*	*	
Skillful	*	*	*	*	*	
	Experienced Experienced Experienced Skillful	Experienced ★ Experienced ★ Experienced ★ Skillful ★	Experienced	Experienced	Experienced	Experienced

## **COURSES**

Apr 2021 - Present Google UX Design

Google Career Certificates from Coursera

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021 An Introduction of Watercolor Painting

NTNU Extension, School of Continuing Education

Sep 2020 - Feb 2021 An Introduction of Oil Painting

NTNU Extension, School of Continuing Education